Joshua Gomberoff

(929)-302-0833 | joshuagomberoff@gmail.com GitHub: jgombero | LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/joshua-gomberoff

SUMMARY

I'm Josh Gomberoff, a hardworking junior developer with strong ability in JavaScript and Ruby, and am equally comfortable in front and back end developing. Coming from a rich education and background in music performance, I offer a unique skill set in team communication and collaboration, and have the experience to thrive both in new unfamiliar situations and under pressure. My passion for software development stems from the same place as my passion for music making: working together with like-minded individuals to create a product whose whole is greater than the sum of its parts.

RECENT EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Paint Crew Member May, 2019 – Aug, 2019

Cast & Crew Entertainment Service | Vancouver, BC

- Collaborated with 3 other team members to meet strict project completion deadlines.
- Painted walls and other surfaces using traditional and sprayer methods and worked efficiently to complete jobs within required time frames.

Chamber Music Apprentice

Jun, 2019 – Jul, 2019

Valley of the Moon Music Festival | Sonoma, CA

- Collaborated with 4 other apprentices in rehearsals in preparation for community outreach concerts and other large featured performances
- Collaborated, was coached by, and performed alongside world renown string chamber musicians and soloists

Facilities Coordinator May, 2018 – Jun 2018

Maximus Canada | Victoria, BC

- Monitored office inventory to maintain adequate supply levels and order products
- Handles all delegated tasks, including taking warehouse storage inventory and general office equipment setup and repair

EDUCATION

Manhattan School of Music | Professional Studies Certificate May 2020

• GPA: 4.0

Manhattan School of Music | Master of Music | May 2019

• GPA: 4.0

University of Victoria | Bachelor of Music May 2017

SKILLS

Languages: JavaScript, Ruby, HTML, CSS

Frameworks, Libraries, and Environments: NodeJS, ReactJS, Rails, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery

Systems, CMS, and Databases: SQL, Git

Testing: Mocha, Chai, Jest, Storybook, Cypress

Spoken Languages: English, French

Strong Team Related Communication

PROJECTS

Interview Scheduler

- https://github.com/jgombero/scheduler
- A Scheduler that lets the user create, edit, and delete appointments
- Front-end: HTML, CSS, React
- Back-end: Node, Express, SQL
- Test: Jest, Storybook, Cypress

Tweeter

- A simplified single-page Twitter clone
- Front-end: HTML, CSS, jQuery, AJAX, JavaScript
- Back-end: Node, Express, MongoDB

TinyApp

- Web application that allows users to shorten long URLs
- Front-end: HTML, JavaScript, EJS
- Back-end: Node, Express

https://github.com/jgombero/tweeter

https://github.com/jgombero/tinyapp